<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Etched Press</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://etchedpress.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://etchedpress.com/</id><updated>2023-12-24T23:59:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>not my daughter by Jessie Scrimager Galloway</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/not-my-daughter-jessie-galloway.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-12-24T23:59:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-12-24T23:59:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Etched Press Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2023-12-24:/shop/not-my-daughter-jessie-galloway.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Available for Pre-Order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Ships January 22, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;not my daughter&lt;/em&gt; by Jessie Scrimager Galloway is a full-length collection of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-21-2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not my daughter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a mesmerizing collection of 44 poems that are part confessional, part documentary, part analytical lyric exploration of the adoption system,  part southern baptist parentage …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Available for Pre-Order&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Ships January 22, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;not my daughter&lt;/em&gt; by Jessie Scrimager Galloway is a full-length collection of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-21-2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not my daughter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a mesmerizing collection of 44 poems that are part confessional, part documentary, part analytical lyric exploration of the adoption system,  part southern baptist parentage and queer identity narrative, part psychedelic sensual love story of the self and others, part meditation on loss and processing of grief with a complicated relationship, part, part, part. As you will find throughout, “this is my body, / broken for you,” it contains multitudes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jessie is a poetic auteur of technical brilliance, singular personality, and deep interior meaning who immerses the reader in a universe through the use of her textured world which, even though it’s only a slice, feels whole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/VyNamsaYqLo?si=BWILgyoQ0fKmthkL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“With crisp lyricism and narration, not my daughter slices dogma and illuminates the power of resiliency. This book is a must-have for living in this world and claiming your sexuality, your name, your life no matter what. Jessie’s poems redefine daughterhood and embrace what we humans long for, always, love.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–Thea Matthews, author of &lt;em&gt;Unearth [The Flowers]&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The queer-adopted-kid-poet-who-teaches-creative-writing in me swoons over the brilliant craft and the precise play with language. I’ll return to this collection again and again. I want to use every poem as an example of “this is how you truth.” These poems give us somewhere to belong and make us feel less alone.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–Su Flatt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Jessie's lines of poetry are glass castles; ready to shatter over you again and again. She elicits a yearning, that is delicate and eternal, from tender moments that can make—or break—a life: a ripped saccharine packet lying prostrate on a table, a fork scraping the rim of a plate, the pluck of fishnet threads marking a thigh.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–Andrea Passwater&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“This debut collection presents a brilliant examination of three languages: heritage, erasure, and wonder. Here, you’ll see a poet in the crossfire of the human experience. This work cuts with precision crafting a map that resonates with raw authenticity. Jessie weaves a narrative that is both haunting and deeply moving. This book is a must-read.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–Antony Fangary, author of &lt;em&gt;Haram&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessie Scrimager Galloway&lt;/strong&gt; is an adopted, queer poet with mommy issues. She is a graduate of Pacific University’s MFA program and author of the chapbook &lt;em&gt;Liminal: A Life of Cleavage&lt;/em&gt; (Lost Horse Press, 2006). She loves her wife’s fried chicken and enjoys riveting conversations with her best editor: Snacks, a wily, polydactyl, orange cat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/static/images/jessie-galloway.jpg" alt="Jessie Galloway author photo by Reina Vazquez" style="height:150px; width:auto;" /&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Jessie Scrimage Galloway&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Full-Length"></category></entry><entry><title>how we liberated what secrets we modified by john compton</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/how-we-liberated-john-compton.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2023-03-10T19:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2023-03-10T19:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Etched Press Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2023-03-10:/shop/how-we-liberated-john-compton.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now Available&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;how we liberated what secrets we modified&lt;/em&gt; by john compton is a chapbook-length collection of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-93584-717-5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;how we liberated what secrets we modified&lt;/em&gt; is a book of the body and of the mind. john compton writes in a loose but raw style with poems that show …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now Available&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;how we liberated what secrets we modified&lt;/em&gt; by john compton is a chapbook-length collection of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-93584-717-5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;how we liberated what secrets we modified&lt;/em&gt; is a book of the body and of the mind. john compton writes in a loose but raw style with poems that show “lust drips tenderly like a sadistic flower.” Across 17 poems, readers witness the force of an insatiable imagination meeting an immovable resolve. These poems make the page tremble like aftershocks of an earthquake. &lt;em&gt;how we liberated what secrets we modified&lt;/em&gt; is erotic, filled with the remnants of desire and betrayal. This is poetry where even “the birds, keep  plague / pollinate the air. / each toxic breath / determines / a second-guessed inhale.” Be prepared for a journey through a beautiful world where "birds, devastated refugees, / scratch across the sky / longing to find a home."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“how we liberated what secrets we modified is full of frank, aching particulars, the terror “nonconsensual,” even the birds “devastated refugees.” john compton’s cutting lines disclose as much as they contradict: “i don’t want to die / yet living isn’t enough.” This is a sensual, brash book of the mathematics of oblivion—and compton reminds us that our number is up.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;—&lt;em&gt;Randall Mann, author of A Better Life (2021).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“how we liberated what secrets we modified is a book of solar flares that perturb + disturb the standard signals of love, death, sickness, lust, &amp;amp; trauma. In these poems, john compton explores the many ways "distance becomes an orbit / while air fluctuates." This is the miasmatic air of Baudelaire's city as much as it is Stefan George's air of another planet, or the wind we can almost hear rattling in the background while John Wieners writes in his "A Poem for Trapped Things": "Gasping for breath. / Living for the instant." The poet's breath is held in &amp;amp; let go, "a singular / bubble within a spectrum / of time continuously writing" new queer histories that disseminate by word of mouth, on bathroom walls, or "scratch[ed] across the sky". Every corner of the universe where desire may hope to go, john compton has already been. We're just lucky he left us a trail.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;—&lt;em&gt;Tom Snarsky, author of Light-Up Swan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“In john compton’s dark and insatiable imagination, our bodies turn to bones and dirt, the mind becomes a one-eyed lighthouse, an IV figured as a marionette’s strings. Like the visual art of their patron saint Salvador Dali, these poems distort experience into something mesmerizing and grotesque. Elegiac, aching, innocent, unforgettable, compton’s poems are fearless, even as “the air beats down. // the air beats us down.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;—&lt;em&gt;Richie Hofmann, A Hundred Lovers: Poems&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/poetjohncompton"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;john compton&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (b. 1987) is a gay poet who lives in kentucky with his husband josh and their dogs and cats. He is the author of two full-length collections &lt;em&gt;trainride elsewhere&lt;/em&gt; (Pressed Wafer, 2016) and &lt;em&gt;the castration of a minor god&lt;/em&gt; (Ghost City Press, 2022) as well as ten chapbooks, including &lt;em&gt;a child growing wild inside the mothering womb&lt;/em&gt; (Ghost City Press, 2020), &lt;em&gt;i saw god cooking children / paint their bones&lt;/em&gt; (Blood Pudding Press 2020), and the forthcoming &lt;em&gt;melancholy arcadia&lt;/em&gt; (Small Harbor Press, May 2024) and &lt;em&gt;blacked out borderland from an exponential crisis&lt;/em&gt; (Ethel Zine and Micro Press, Sep 2023). His pdf chapbook &lt;em&gt;the skies fell revelations&lt;/em&gt; is free &lt;a href="https://ghostcitypress.com/books/the-castration-of-a-minor-god"&gt;when you purchase his full length poetry book from Ghost City Press&lt;/a&gt;. He has been nominated for three pushcart prizes and published in numerous magazines and anthologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="/static/images/john-compton.jpg" alt="john compton author photo" style="height:150px; width:auto;" /&gt;
&lt;center&gt;john compton&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Etched Press Chapbook Bundle</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/chapbook-bundle.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-08-23T17:42:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-08-23T17:42:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2020-08-23:/shop/chapbook-bundle.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Recieve a bundle of 3 chapbooks for the price of 2!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll receive a bundle of chapbooks from 3 of the following:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This Frayed Universe by Sarah Brashear&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Singing is My Favorite Part by Susan Elliott Brown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haram by Antony Fangary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apart from Concrete Existence by Josef Krebs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flotsam by …&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Recieve a bundle of 3 chapbooks for the price of 2!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You'll receive a bundle of chapbooks from 3 of the following:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This Frayed Universe by Sarah Brashear&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Singing is My Favorite Part by Susan Elliott Brown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haram by Antony Fangary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apart from Concrete Existence by Josef Krebs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flotsam by Catherine Kyle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Poems in Which I am Chopped up by Zack Rearick&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Girl with the Green Violin by Kirby Wright&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let us know if there is one book that you'd specifically like&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Bundles"></category></entry><entry><title>Haram by Antony Fangary</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/haram-antony-fangary.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-12-12T21:08:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-12-12T21:08:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Etched Press Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2018-12-12:/shop/haram-antony-fangary.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Haram&lt;/em&gt; by Antony Fangary is a chapbook-length collection of poems &amp;amp; prayers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-93584-715-1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Through even psychic journeys home, Fangary quarries the oaths we have grown numb to. Hiding from no one, here is a wanderer who has written poems on the film layer of his eyes. In the war and …&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Haram&lt;/em&gt; by Antony Fangary is a chapbook-length collection of poems &amp;amp; prayers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-93584-715-1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Through even psychic journeys home, Fangary quarries the oaths we have grown numb to. Hiding from no one, here is a wanderer who has written poems on the film layer of his eyes. In the war and peace of imperialist myth, poems written on behalf of we who don’t exist. And gentle paper for the prayers of our grandmothers’ tongues.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Tongo Eisen-Martin, author of the American Book Award winning&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Antony Fangary has a unique and harrowing American story to tell. His masterstroke as author was to alternate Coptic prayers with personal revelation: “my father was proud of my skin when I was born / my mother says he showed me to everyone in the hospital / a brown man with a son white as an ostrich egg / the American dream //  Lord, look with / Merciful eyes / At my weakness / At my disgrace.” This book is the perfect example of the literature we should be reading, to open our eyes to the world and thereby to know ourselves.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Paul Hoover, editor of Postmodern American Poetry: A Norton Anthology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antony Fangary&lt;/strong&gt; holds an MFA from San Francisco State University and is a recipient of the Ina Coolbrith Poetry Prize. You can also find his recent work in &lt;em&gt;Waccamaw, The Bookends Review, Anomaly, Welter&lt;/em&gt;, and more. He is curator of the &lt;em&gt;Tenderlovin’ in the TL&lt;/em&gt; reading series. The series also serves as a community outreach program that provides charity for displaced individuals in the Tenderloin neighborhood of San Francisco. You can learn more about Antony at his website: &lt;a href="http://www.antonyfangary.com/"&gt;www.antonyfangary.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Author-Photo-150x150.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="Antony-Fangary-Author-Photo" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2018/12/Author-Photo-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Antony Fangary&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Apart from Concrete Existence by Josef Krebs</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/josef-krebs-concrete.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-01-08T19:18:00-08:00</published><updated>2016-01-08T19:18:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Etched Press Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2016-01-08:/shop/josef-krebs-concrete.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apart from Concrete Existence&lt;/em&gt; by Josef Krebs is a chapbook-length collection of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-13-7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Josef Krebs’&lt;/strong&gt; poetry appears in &lt;em&gt;Agenda, Bicycle Review, Calliope, Mouse Tales Press, The Corner Club Press, The FictionWeek Literary Review&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Burningword Literary Journal&lt;/em&gt;. His fiction has been published by blazeVOX and &lt;em&gt;Apart from Concrete …&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apart from Concrete Existence&lt;/em&gt; by Josef Krebs is a chapbook-length collection of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-13-7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Josef Krebs’&lt;/strong&gt; poetry appears in &lt;em&gt;Agenda, Bicycle Review, Calliope, Mouse Tales Press, The Corner Club Press, The FictionWeek Literary Review&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Burningword Literary Journal&lt;/em&gt;. His fiction has been published by blazeVOX and &lt;em&gt;Apart from Concrete Existence &lt;/em&gt;is his first chapbook. Krebs is the author of three novels, five screenplays, and another book of poetry. He is also a filmmaker who has had films screened at the Santa Cruz and Cannes film festivals. He lives and works in New York as a freelance writer for Sound &amp;amp; Vision magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Josef.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="josef-krebs" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Josef-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Josef Krebs&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>This Frayed Universe by Sarah Brashear</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/sarah-brashear-frayed.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-01-08T15:45:00-08:00</published><updated>2016-01-08T15:45:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2016-01-08:/shop/sarah-brashear-frayed.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This Frayed Universe is a chapbook of poems by Sarah Brashear on the human condition of coping with our beautiful and heavy world.
This Frayed Universe is a chapbook of poems by Sarah Brashear.&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This Frayed Universe&lt;/em&gt; is a chapbook of poems by Sarah Brashear. It describes our heavy and beautiful world and the crisis of the ordinary human coping with the everyday effects of life. Brashear’s rich language shows that not only is being a person a blessing, but at times, an unexpected disaster. Through her strong images, she is able to illustrate what many other authors have also shown—that within the unordinary is the ordinary, and that perhaps this insanity we diagnose in others is actually our sanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-11-3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sarah Brashear&lt;/strong&gt; lives in Pennsylvania and has an MFA in Creative Writing from Chatham University. Her first full-length book of poetry, &lt;em&gt;On Beacon Street&lt;/em&gt;, was published by &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Beacon-Street-Sarah-Brashear/dp/1682640035/"&gt;Cawing Crow Press&lt;/a&gt;. She is currently a writing instructor at Lebanon Valley College. When she isn’t writing or teaching, she enjoys playing tennis and going to concerts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/authphoto.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="Sarah-Brashear" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2016/01/authphoto-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Sarah Brashear&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbook"></category></entry><entry><title>The Girl with the Green Violin by Kirby Wright</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/kirby-wright-green.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2015-10-02T16:15:00-07:00</published><updated>2015-10-02T16:15:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2015-10-02:/shop/kirby-wright-green.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Girl with the Green Violin is a chapbook of poems&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Girl with the Green Violin&lt;/em&gt; is a chapbook of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-07-6&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kirby Wright&lt;/strong&gt; was born and raised in Honolulu, Hawaii. He is a graduate of Punahou School in Honolulu and the University of California at San Diego. He received his MFA in Creative Writing from San Francisco State University. Wright has been nominated for five Pushcart Prizes and three Best of the Webs. Wright is a past recipient of the Ann Fields Poetry Prize, the Academy of American Poets Award, the Browning Society Award for Dramatic Monologue, and Arts Council Silicon Valley Fellowships in Poetry and The Novel. Excluding &lt;em&gt;The Girl with the Green Violin,&lt;/em&gt; He is the author of eight full-length collections including &lt;em&gt;Notes Above Water, Selected Poems&lt;/em&gt; (Lemon Shark Press, 2014) and three other chapbooks. You can read more about Wright on his &lt;a href="http://kibs33.wix.com/kirbywright"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2015/10/wright.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="Kirby-Wright" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2015/10/wright-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;center&gt;Kirby Wright&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Singing is My Favorite by Susan Elliott Brown</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/susan-elliott-brown-singing.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2015-10-02T16:14:00-07:00</published><updated>2015-10-02T16:14:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2015-10-02:/shop/susan-elliott-brown-singing.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Singing Is My Favorite Part &lt;/em&gt;is a chapbook of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-09-0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also available &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Singing-Favorite-Etched-Press-Poetry-ebook/dp/B0161CE6O6"&gt;on Kindle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Susan Elliott Brown’s poems are so whip-smart, so elegant I need to dress up to read them. I’d like to take them to a Montmartre café so they can feel the …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Singing Is My Favorite Part &lt;/em&gt;is a chapbook of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-09-0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also available &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Singing-Favorite-Etched-Press-Poetry-ebook/dp/B0161CE6O6"&gt;on Kindle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Susan Elliott Brown’s poems are so whip-smart, so elegant I need to dress up to read them. I’d like to take them to a Montmartre café so they can feel the sun of Paris as I savor each with coffee and croissant. I’d like to make them my tiny house, and open my eyes to them every day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;–Angela Ball, author of &lt;em&gt;The Night Clerk at the Hotel of Both Worlds&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Susan Elliott Brown&lt;/strong&gt; is a PhD student at the University of Southern Mississippi where she received the 2014 Joan Johnson Award in Poetry. &lt;em&gt;The Singing is My Favorite Part&lt;/em&gt; is her debut chapbook. Her poems have appeared or are forthcoming in &lt;em&gt;The Best American Poetry&lt;/em&gt; blog, Measure&lt;em&gt;: A Review of Formal Poetry, The Atticus Review, The Ampersand Review&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Alehouse&lt;/em&gt;, among others. You can follow her on Twitter &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/selliottbrown"&gt;@selliottbrown&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2015/10/susan_e_brown.png"&gt;&lt;img alt="susan-elliott-brown" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2015/10/susan_e_brown-150x150.png" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;center&gt;Susan Elliott Brown&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Flotsam by Catherine Kyle</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/flotsam-catherine-kyle.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2015-02-09T01:43:00-08:00</published><updated>2015-02-09T01:43:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2015-02-09:/shop/flotsam-catherine-kyle.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Flotsam by Catherine Kyle is a chapbook of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/kyle-flotsam.pdf"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-05-2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Kyle affirms women’s stories, as well as womanhood in general. And, most pressing, a woman's firm, fierce desire to be her own person."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-H.L. Nelson, author of The Sea is Only Meat, on Catherine …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Flotsam by Catherine Kyle is a chapbook of poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/kyle-flotsam.pdf"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1935847-05-2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Kyle affirms women’s stories, as well as womanhood in general. And, most pressing, a woman's firm, fierce desire to be her own person."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-H.L. Nelson, author of The Sea is Only Meat, on Catherine Kyle's Work&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catherine Kyle&lt;/strong&gt; is the author of &lt;em&gt;Fulgurite&lt;/em&gt; (Cornerstone Press, forthcoming), &lt;em&gt;Shelter in Place&lt;/em&gt; (Spuyten Duyvil, 2019), and other poetry collections. Her writing has appeared in &lt;em&gt;Bellingham Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Colorado Review&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Mid-American Review&lt;/em&gt;, and other journals. She was the winner of the 2019-2020 COG Poetry Award, a finalist for the 2021 Mississippi Review Prize in poetry, and a finalist for the 2021 Pinch Literary Awards. She is an assistant professor at DigiPen Institute of Technology, where she teaches creative writing. Her hybrid-genre chapbook &lt;em&gt;Feral Domesticity&lt;/em&gt;, which contains poetry, fiction, and paintings, was published by &lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/186798579/feral-domesticity-by-catherine-kyle?ref=listing-shop-header-0"&gt;Robocup Press&lt;/a&gt;. You can read more about Catherine on her website: &lt;a href="http://www.catherinebaileykyle.com"&gt;www.catherinebaileykyle.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/catherine_kyle.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="catherine-kyle" class="size-full" height="135" src="../wp-content/uploads/2015/02/catherine_kyle.jpg" width="135"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Catherine Kyle&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Poems in Which I Am by Zack Rearick</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/zack-rearick-poems.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2013-05-14T21:29:00-07:00</published><updated>2013-05-14T21:29:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2013-05-14:/shop/zack-rearick-poems.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Poems in Which I Am Chopped up, Stepped on, and Sleep Deprived&lt;/em&gt; is a chapbook of poems by Zack Rearick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2013/05/rearick-poems.pdf"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-02-1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also available &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Chopped-Stepped-Deprived-Etched-Poetry-ebook/dp/B00BFSGJYW"&gt;on Kindle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zack Rearick&lt;/strong&gt; is a Ph.D. student in Literary Studies at Georgia State University. He obtained his Master of Arts in …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Poems in Which I Am Chopped up, Stepped on, and Sleep Deprived&lt;/em&gt; is a chapbook of poems by Zack Rearick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2013/05/rearick-poems.pdf"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-02-1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also available &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.com/Chopped-Stepped-Deprived-Etched-Poetry-ebook/dp/B00BFSGJYW"&gt;on Kindle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zack Rearick&lt;/strong&gt; is a Ph.D. student in Literary Studies at Georgia State University. He obtained his Master of Arts in English at the University of North Carolina at Wilmington. He cultivates his passion for poetry via public readings of his own work and those of his favorite poets, including Plath, Barrett Browning, Sexton, Manley Hopkins, and Keats. &lt;em&gt;Poems in Which I Am Chopped Up, Stepped On and Sleep Deprived &lt;/em&gt;is his first chapbook. He currently resides in Atlanta, Georgia. Learn more about Zack and the &lt;a href="https://bloodbankblues.wordpress.com/category/the-american-canon/"&gt;American Literary Canon&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2013/05/zack_rearick.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="zack-rearick" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2013/05/zack_rearick-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Zack Rearick&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Before OnStar by Sarah Carson</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/before-onstar-by-sarah-carson.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2010-05-15T01:04:00-07:00</published><updated>2010-05-15T01:04:00-07:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2010-05-15:/shop/before-onstar-by-sarah-carson.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Before OnStar&lt;/em&gt; by Sarah Carson is a short collection of prose poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="..static/pdf/before-carson.pdf"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-00-7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Every single poem in &lt;em&gt;Before OnStar&lt;/em&gt; rattles around the corner like a firetruck on three wheels, siren blaring."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Michael Dennis at &lt;a href="http://michaeldennispoet.blogspot.ca/2015/08/before-onstar-sarah-carson-etched-press.html"&gt;Today's Book of Poetry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Sarah Carson has an imaginative gift for transporting …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Before OnStar&lt;/em&gt; by Sarah Carson is a short collection of prose poems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="..static/pdf/before-carson.pdf"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-00-7&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Every single poem in &lt;em&gt;Before OnStar&lt;/em&gt; rattles around the corner like a firetruck on three wheels, siren blaring."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Michael Dennis at &lt;a href="http://michaeldennispoet.blogspot.ca/2015/08/before-onstar-sarah-carson-etched-press.html"&gt;Today's Book of Poetry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Sarah Carson has an imaginative gift for transporting us within the nuances &amp;amp; netherworld of her hometown. I can’t imagine a more dead-eye illumination of the region—told with incredible wit &amp;amp; a rough-minded passion. Many might steer you from the town itself, but missing out on Buick City would be a decidedly wrong turn. I will gladly enjoy returning to these pages—and often."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;-Ben Hamper, author of &lt;em&gt;Rivethead,&lt;/em&gt; on Sarah Carson's work&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.stuffsarahwrote.com/"&gt;Sarah Carson&lt;/a&gt; was born and raised in Michigan but now lives in Chicago where she works at a church. Her poetry and short stories have appeared in &lt;em&gt;Cream City Review, Columbia Poetry Review, Diagram, Guernica&lt;/em&gt;, and the &lt;em&gt;Nashville Review&lt;/em&gt;, among others. She is also the author of three chapbooks and the full-length collections: &lt;em&gt;Buick City&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href="http://mayapplepress.com/sarah-carson-buick-city/"&gt;Mayapple Press&lt;/a&gt;) and &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://batcatpress.com/publications/piwyd/"&gt;Poems in which You Die&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (Bat Cat Press). She blogs at &lt;a href="http://sarahamycarson.wordpress.com"&gt;sarahamycarson.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2010/05/Sarah-Carson.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="before-onstar-by-sarah-carson" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2010/05/Sarah-Carson-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Sarah Carson&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry><entry><title>Bright Burning Fuse by Melanie Faith</title><link href="https://etchedpress.com/shop/bright-burning-fuse-by-melanie-faith.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2010-01-15T21:11:00-08:00</published><updated>2010-01-15T21:11:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Editor</name></author><id>tag:etchedpress.com,2010-01-15:/shop/bright-burning-fuse-by-melanie-faith.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bright, Burning Fuse&lt;/em&gt; by Melanie Faith is the first chapbook in the Etched Press Poetry Series published in December 2008. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../static/bright-excerpt.pdf" title="Excerpt"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-01-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Melanie's poems describe a variety of awakenings...find beginnings, even in the sparest of places."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Jessie Carty, author of &lt;/em&gt;Practicing Disaster&lt;em&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;/em&gt;Paper House&lt;em&gt;, on the …&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bright, Burning Fuse&lt;/em&gt; by Melanie Faith is the first chapbook in the Etched Press Poetry Series published in December 2008. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../static/bright-excerpt.pdf" title="Excerpt"&gt;Read an excerpt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ISBN: 978-1-935847-01-4&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"Melanie's poems describe a variety of awakenings...find beginnings, even in the sparest of places."&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Jessie Carty, author of &lt;/em&gt;Practicing Disaster&lt;em&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;/em&gt;Paper House&lt;em&gt;, on the work of Melanie Faith&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Melanie Faith&lt;/strong&gt; holds an M.F.A. in Creative Writing from Queens University of Charlotte, NC. Her poetry and photography has appeared in &lt;em&gt;The Binnacle&lt;/em&gt; (University of Maine), &lt;em&gt;Emprise Review, Heavyglow, Six Little Things, Mo: Writings From The River&lt;/em&gt; (Montana State University), and more. Her instructional article about creative writing critique groups was published in &lt;em&gt;The Writer&lt;/em&gt; magazine (November 2009). The opening poem from the collection (along with landscape photos taken by the author) is featured in the online literary magazine, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/shapeofabox"&gt;Shape of a Box&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by &lt;a href="http://www.folded.wordpress.com"&gt;Folded Word Press&lt;/a&gt;. She lives and writes in rural Pennsylvania, where she educates young minds as an English, History, and SAT tutor at a college preparatory high school. You can read more about Melanie on her website: &lt;a href="https://www.melaniedfaith.com/"&gt;www.melaniedfaith.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../wp-content/uploads/2010/01/Melanie_Faith.jpg"&gt;&lt;img alt="melanie-faith" class="size-thumbnail" height="150" src="../wp-content/uploads/2010/01/Melanie_Faith-150x150.jpg" width="150"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;center&gt;Melanie Faith&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="Chapbooks"></category></entry></feed>